palacejobs.com 2011-06-20

# Privacy Policy

## Purpose Of Collection Of Personal Data

Personal data submitted by Jobseeker will be used for the sole purpose of assisting him/her to find appropriate employment with Employer and assisting Employer to assess the suitability of candidates for a job vacancy in the manner specified on our [Job Seekers - Service Guide](http://www.jobsdb.com.hk/HK/en/StaticContentfullcontainer/ServiceGuide.htm) web page.

The Company collects information about the user that is personally identifiable like name, address, email address, phone number and demographic information including country, age, sex that is not otherwise publicly available. Occasionally, the Company may also collect additional personal data from user in connection with contests, surveys, or special offers.

## Transfer of Data

The personal data of Jobseeker will only be transmitted and disclosed to corporate clients of the Company (for the purpose specified in the preceding paragraph or any directly related purpose) which have made specific requests for such data only if and when Jobseeker has given his/her prior consent.

## Subscription of Newsletter/Marketing Materials

Users of the Web Site can sign up or unsubscribe for newsletters and any other marketing materials by:- 

(1) logging into registration or user account maintenance web pages; or 

(2) clicking on the automatic link appearing in each newsletter/message.

## Legal Disclaimer

The Company reserves the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when the Company believes that disclosure is necessary to protect the Company's rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on the Web Site.

## Access

Jobseeker is entitled to make a data access or correction request concerning his/her own personal data (subject to prior confirmation of identity) kept with the Company. Alternatively, Jobseeker may edit or amend such personal data at any time by logging onto the Site via the My Resume section of the Web Site.

## Cookies

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user's computer for record-keeping purposes. The Company uses cookies on the Web Site. The Company does not link the cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on the Web Site.

The Company uses both session cookies and persistent cookies. The Company uses session cookies to make it easier for you to navigate the Web Site. A session cookie expires when you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser's "help" file.

## Log Files

As is true of most web sites, the Company gathers certain information automatically and stores it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data.

The Company uses this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users' movements around the Web Site and to gather demographic information about the Web Site's user base as a whole.

The Company does not link this automatically-collected data to personally identifiable information.

The Company uses a third-party tracking service called Google Analytics that uses cookies to track non-personally identifiable information about visitors to the Web Site in the aggregate, such as page view, number of unique visitors, most visited pages, etc.

## Links to Other Sites

This Web Site contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by the Company. Please be aware that the Company is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites.

The Company encourages you to be aware when you leave the Web Site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information.

This privacy statement applies only to information collected by this Web Site.

## Testimonials

The Company posts user's testimonials on the Web Site which may contain personally identifiable information such as the user's name. The Company does obtain the users consent prior to posting the testimonial to post their name along with their testimonial

## Security

The security of your personal information is important to the Company. When you enter sensitive information, such as credit card number, on the Company's order forms, the Company encrypts that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). We use a third party service provider to facilitate these transactions on the Site.

The Company follows generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to it, both during transmission and once the Company receives it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while the Company strives to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, the Company cannot guarantee its absolute security.

If you have any questions about security on the Web Site, you can send email to the Company using the email addresses found in the Contact Us link in the Web Site

## Retention of Personal Details

Subject to legal requirements and the refusal of Jobseeker, the personal data of Jobseeker will be retained by the Company after deactivation of the relevant service until Jobseeker formally requests the Company to erase his/her own personal data from the Company's Database.

The Jobseeker can delete or correct his or her own personal data by logging into their account and changing their information via the My Resume section of the Website.

## Changes in this Privacy Statement

If the Company decides to change its privacy policy, the Company will post those changes to this Privacy Statement, the page, and other places the Company deems appropriate so that you are aware of what information the Company collects, how the Company uses it, and under what circumstances, if any, the Company discloses it.

The Company reserves the right to modify this Privacy Statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If the Company make material changes to this policy, the Company will notify the user here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page.
